LUIS RODRÍGUEZ BALTODANO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+2 years experience as a Frontend Developer, planning, building and maintaining interactive web applications with high performance code.+1 year of experience as a Backend Developer, developing REST API and applications with MVC architecture, with technologies such as Java, Spring boot, SQL and knowledge of C#. I have worked directly with clients for project planning and implementing new features. I have encountered various challenges such as working in diverse areas and with different teams, in which I have been able to adapt successfully.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer at Accenture

December 2021 - Present

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Planning, development, and maintenance of a digital web Vehicles platform.
- Maintenance of web applications, applying code fixing and refactoring.
- Understand and meet the requirements in the established times with high performance code.
- Efficient teamwork to deliver value to the custumer.

Tech Stack: VueJs, ReactJs Sass, Bootstrap, Java, Spring Boot, C#, Git, AEM, Confluence, Jira, Microsoft Teams.

Software Developer Internship at Accenture

August 2021 - November 2021

RESPONSIBILITIES

- Development and maintenance of a project planning platform.
- Meeting requirements within established deadlines.
- Development of new features and design using best practices and clean code.
- Adaptation to new challenges and technologies, delivering value to the customer.
- Work efficiently as a team helping each other and delivering value to the customer.

Tech Stack: Angular, Typescript, Sass, Java, Spring Boot, Figma, Microsoft Teams.

SKILLS

- HTML / CSS
- Javascript / Typescript
- React Js / Next Js
- Vue Js

- Git
- Java / Spring Boot
- C#
- SQL / MySQL

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptivity
- Communication
- Teamwork

- Resilience
- Critical Thinking
- Problem-Solving

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Systems at Universidad Nacional de Costa Rica February 2018 - November 2021

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- English (B2)